[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a movie about a mathematician who develops a formula that predicts the prices of stock markets?", "correct_answer": "The Bank", "incorrect_answers": ["The Puzzle", "The Formula", "The Tricks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the science fiction Soylent Green, who starred as Detective Robert Thorn?", "correct_answer": "Charlton Heston", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Diuglas", "Kirk Douglas", "Burt Lancaster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which disease is treated by Synthroid (levothyroxine)?", "correct_answer": "Hypothyroidism", "incorrect_answers": ["Multiple Sclerosis", "Congestive Heart Failure", "Erectile Dysfunction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the atomic number of the chemical element chlorine?", "correct_answer": "17", "incorrect_answers": ["28", "83", "9"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which sitcom aired on ABC from 1952 to 1966 after a ten-year run on radio?", "correct_answer": "Ozzie and Harriet", "incorrect_answers": ["Friends", "The Simpsons", "Frasier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Titanic, written and directed by James Cameron, was nominated for 11 Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which animals have the most unique species endemic to Australia?", "correct_answer": "Amphibians", "incorrect_answers": ["Mammals", "Insects", "Reptiles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tom Cruise had a lead role in all, but one of these movies.  Which one?", "correct_answer": "Endless Love", "incorrect_answers": ["Rain Man", "The Firm", "Magnolia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these beautiful African American singers plays a leading role in the 2003 movie The Fighting Temptations?", "correct_answer": "Beyonce Knowles", "incorrect_answers": ["Toni Braxton", "Brandy", "Ashanti"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is considered the Father of Modern Dentistry?", "correct_answer": "Pierre Fauchard", "incorrect_answers": ["Horace Wells", "Lucien Hobbs", "Norman Kingsley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Team America: World Police, where does the team of U.S. Special Forces stay when they are not fighting crime?", "correct_answer": "Mount Rushmore", "incorrect_answers": ["The Grand Canyon", "The basement of The White House", "The Statue of Liberty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Yellow River in China is prone to flooding.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]